Your Majesty, why did you summon back the 1000 elite soldiers
جلالة الملك ، لماذا استدعت 1000 جندي من النخبة
I sent to suppress bandits?
أرسلت لقمع قطاع الطرق؟
Of course it's because of an emergency.
بالطبع هذا بسبب حالة طارئة.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Advisor, maybe you don't know,
مستشار ، ربما لا تعرف ،
but those City Lords next door,
لكن أباطرة المدينة المجاورين ،
In a few days,
في أيام قليلة،
I'm going to have
أنا سأحصل على
a blind date meeting with thousands of people,
لقاء موعد أعمى مع الآلاف من الناس ،
As a result, we were short of hands,
نتيجة لذلك ، كانت أيدينا ناقصة ،
so we summoned your elite soldiers back urgently.
لذلك استدعينا جنود النخبة على وجه السرعة.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
bandits are rampant in Qingniu Mountain,
ينتشر قطاع الطرق في جبل تشينغنيو ،
It has always been a hidden danger in Black Rock City.
لطالما كان خطرًا خفيًا في مدينة بلاك روك.
Especially the Toad Village,
خاصة قرية العلجوم ،
which is extremely arrogant.
وهو متعجرف للغاية.
They are clearly
هم واضحون
humiliating our Black Rock City this time.
إذلال مدينة بلاك روك هذه المرة.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Don't be mad,
لا تغضب
Advisor. I'll send you another 100 elite soldiers.
مستشار.  سأرسل لك 100 جندي آخر من النخبة.
150,
150 ،
200 will do, right?
200 سيفعل ، أليس كذلك؟
Come on, drink it.
تعال ، اشربه.
Shame and humiliation
الخزي والذل
are improper to live a life.
من غير اللائق أن يعيشوا حياة.
You,
أنت،
Do you know why you failed?
هل تعلم لماذا فشلت؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Did you fight for your faith?
هل جاهدت من أجل إيمانك؟
Are you fighting with the will to die?
هل تحارب مع إرادة الموت؟
Do you have anything to protect?
هل لديك أي شيء لتحميه؟
I have both.
لدي كلاهما.
Then you are wrong.
إذن أنت مخطئ.
That's why you failed.
لهذا السبب فشلت.
Your mind is full of distractions.
عقلك مليء بالإلهاءات.
How to achieve great things?
كيف تحقق أشياء عظيمة؟
How can I get rid of these distractions?
كيف يمكنني التخلص من هذه المشتتات؟
Come to my Toad Village.
تعال إلى قرية العلجوم الخاصة بي.
Starting from scratch,
تبدأ من الصفر،
I'll teach you slowly.
سأعلمك ببطء.
A treacherous young man.
شاب غادر.
Under the condition of exploiting the loopholes in the system,
بشرط استغلال الثغرات في النظام ،
you completed
أكملت
the task of defending Toad Village 10 times,
مهمة الدفاع عن قرية العلجوم 10 مرات ،
At the same time, I also completed the hidden task.
في نفس الوقت ، أكملت أيضًا المهمة المخفية.
Assemble Lin Shaoyu
تجميع لين شاويو
to merge and reward the mysterious treasure.
لدمج ومكافأة الكنز الغامض.
Master,
يتقن،
we've searched everywhere in the stockade,
بحثنا في كل مكان في الحاجز ،
What kind of treasure is there?
ما هو نوع الكنز الموجود؟
I've told you.
لقد قلت لك.
When we broke up two days ago,
عندما انفصلنا قبل يومين ،
I searched the whole stockade.
لقد فتشت الحاجز كله.
I would have seen it a long time ago.
كنت سأراه منذ وقت طويل.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
The system has no reason to lie to me.
النظام ليس لديه سبب للكذب علي.
A frustrated young man.
شاب محبط.
There's a new mission.
هناك مهمة جديدة.
Hey,
يا،
I was just looking for you.
كنت أبحث عنك فقط.
Where is the treasure hidden?
أين الكنز الخفي؟
Since it's a mysterious treasure,
لأنه كنز غامض
it won't be easily found by you.
لن تجدها بسهولة.
For now, you'd better focus on
في الوقت الحالي ، من الأفضل أن تركز على
the new defensive mission,
المهمة الدفاعية الجديدة ،
Ah,
آه،
To resist the heavy invasion of Black Rock City,
لمقاومة الغزو العنيف لمدينة بلاك روك ،
you're here again, right?
أنت هنا مرة أخرى ، أليس كذلك؟
It's endless, isn't it?
انها لانهائية ، أليس كذلك؟
You still have one day to prepare.
لا يزال لديك يوم واحد للاستعداد.
Figure it out on your own.
اكتشفها بنفسك.
this time
هذا الوقت
There's no room for you to take advantage of it.
ليس هناك مجال لك للاستفادة منه.
Master is talking to himself again.
المعلم يتحدث إلى نفسه مرة أخرى.
Who are you talking to?
مع من انت تتكلم؟
Everyone,
الجميع،
put those who are looking for treasures aside,
ضعوا أولئك الذين يبحثون عن الكنوز جانبًا ،
I have something more urgent to do.
لدي شيء أكثر إلحاحًا لأفعله.
Master,
يتقن،
only Feihu Village and Gao Feihu are not here,
فقط قرية Feihu و Gao Feihu ليسا هنا ،
No need to wait.
لا داعي للانتظار.
Let's get started.
هيا بنا نبدأ.
Our King of Toad Village has something to say,
ملك قرية العلجوم لديه ما يقوله ،
everyone,
الجميع،
The army of Black Rock City is coming.
جيش بلاك روك سيتي قادم.
Qingniu Mountain is facing a great disaster
يواجه جبل تشينغنيو كارثة كبيرة
and we've gathered everyone here.
وقد جمعنا الجميع هنا.
I just hope that we, Qingniu Mountain,
أنا فقط أتمنى أن نكون ، جبل تشينغنيو ،
can unite as one,
يمكن أن يتحدوا كواحد ،
To defeat the enemy,
لهزيمة العدو ،
we can't defeat so many people in Black Rock City,
لا يمكننا هزيمة الكثير من الناس في بلاك روك سيتي ،
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Is it our Qingniu Mountain that is in trouble?
هل جبل تشينغنيو هو الذي يعاني من مشكلة؟
Or is Toad Village in danger?
أم قرية العلجوم في خطر؟
I've already received an insider
لقد تلقيت بالفعل من الداخل
saying that this time in Black Rock City,
قائلا أن هذه المرة في بلاك روك سيتي ،
They're here for Toad Village.
إنهم هنا من أجل قرية العلجوم.
It has nothing to do with our other stockade.
لا علاقة له بحاجزنا الآخر.
Oh, I see.
حسنا أرى ذلك.
Are you trying to drag us into this?
هل تحاول جرنا إلى هذا؟
Oh,
أوه،
I see.
أرى.
I can't tell that Toad Village is full of bad water,
لا أستطيع أن أقول أن قرية العلجوم مليئة بالمياه السيئة ،
but what if you're afraid?
لكن ماذا لو كنت خائفا؟
You can join our Xinghualing,
يمكنك الانضمام إلى Xinghualing لدينا ،
and the sisters will protect you.
وسوف تحميك الأخوات.
That's right,
صحيح،
Black Rock City,
بلاك روك سيتي ،
He is indeed here to beat our Toad Village.
إنه بالفعل هنا للتغلب على قرية العلجوم.
Haven't you heard, there's no reason
ألم تسمع ، لا يوجد سبب
to lay eggs under the cover of the nest.
لوضع البيض تحت غطاء العش.
What egg?
أي بيضة؟
It's an egg,
إنها بيضة
that is to say,
ذلك بالقول،
After attacking us,
بعد مهاجمتنا ،
it's your turn.
إنه دورك.
Didn't I tell you in the book of flying arrows?
ألم أقل لك في كتاب السهام الطائرة؟
We in Qingniu Mountain have always been in trouble on one side,
نحن في جبل تشينغنيو كنا دائمًا في مشكلة من جانب واحد ،
supported by all sides,
بدعم من جميع الأطراف ،
As long as we complement each other,
طالما نكمل بعضنا البعض ،
no one can defeat
لا أحد يستطيع الهزيمة
our boss,
رئيسنا ،
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
They're all gone.
لقد ذهبوا جميعًا.
There are 200 people on the other side,
هناك 200 شخص على الجانب الآخر ،
but there are only five of us.
لكن لا يوجد سوى خمسة منا.
Master, you're still young,
سيدي ، أنت ما زلت صغيرا ،
but you don't know the benefits of fewer people.
لكنك لا تعرف فوائد قلة الناس.
We just need to be simple,
نحتاج فقط إلى أن نكون بسيطين ،
and in less than a day,
وفي أقل من يوم ،
He will definitely escape to the other end of the mountain.
سوف يهرب بالتأكيد إلى الطرف الآخر من الجبل.
Oh dear,
يا عزيزي،
how can we fear Chief Master before we fight
كيف نخاف من القائد قبل أن نقاتل
and
و
I, Qin Man, will die in battle,
أنا ، تشين مان ، سأموت في المعركة ،
We also need to get some people from Black Rock City to back us up.
نحتاج أيضًا إلى الحصول على بعض الأشخاص من مدينة بلاك روك لدعمنا.
Oh,
أوه،
my back,
ظهري،
I think my back
أعتقد أن ظهري
is broken.
مكسور.
Oh,
أوه،
I can't believe there's a secret door.
لا أصدق أن هناك باب سري.
I advise you
أنا أنصحك
to retreat as soon as possible.
للتراجع في أسرع وقت ممكن.
I have magic power.
لدي قوة سحرية.
But please, Tian Lei,
لكن من فضلك ، تيان لي ،
I didn't expect that Black Rock City,
لم أكن أتوقع أن مدينة بلاك روك ،
You're so overbearing.
أنت متعجرف جدا.
If you don't want to kneel,
إذا كنت لا تريد الركوع ،
just run away.
فقط اهرب.
Lu Hum,
لو هوم
you're rebellious and belligerent,
أنت متمرد ومقاتل ،
Killing innocent people indiscriminately,
قتل الأبرياء دون تمييز ،
today my Toad Village is going to do justice for heaven,
اليوم سوف تقوم قرية العلجوم الخاصة بي بإنصاف الجنة ،